[{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19026"},"rt":18706,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":52130,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19027"},"rt":8921,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":61153,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19028"},"rt":26058,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":87314,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19029"},"rt":27080,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":114494,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1902a"},"rt":52121,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":166717,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1902c"},"rt":7703,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":177550,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1902d"},"rt":22734,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":200383,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1902e"},"rt":66191,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266684,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1902f"},"rt":32765,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":300114,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19030"},"rt":26596,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":326814,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19031"},"rt":11985,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338896,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19032"},"rt":3604,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342605,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19033"},"rt":17083,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":359787,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19034"},"rt":23931,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":383817,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"403 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19035"},"rt":44042,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427975,"subject":"JCKEW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42693","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1904c"},"rt":28246,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":307877,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1904d"},"rt":18503,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":326500,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"F D 11 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1904e"},"rt":8434,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":335042,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"5C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1904f"},"rt":8991,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":344139,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19050"},"rt":19224,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":363472,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I 03 PMI I A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19052"},"rt":16876,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":388681,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"10 AM11 AME G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19053"},"rt":25769,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":414558,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F O O O X X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19054"},"rt":57334,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":472002,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F X 03 PM03 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19055"},"rt":76266,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":548384,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J J I J J J E B B B B 02 PM09 AME B B B F F B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19056"},"rt":10222,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":558913,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"402 PMF E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19057"},"rt":7457,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":566483,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19058"},"rt":10288,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":576876,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F G F B 10 AMG "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19059"},"rt":9617,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":586617,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z Z Z Z E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1905a"},"rt":9415,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":596143,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"303 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1905b"},"rt":10026,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":606278,"subject":"NBR5N","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37698","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19084"},"rt":61135,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":168196,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AMA 11 AMA A O O O 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19085"},"rt":27809,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":196326,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"D 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19086"},"rt":29509,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":225961,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"C C 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19087"},"rt":34133,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":260207,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"U U U F F F F G F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19088"},"rt":14120,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":274437,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1908a"},"rt":9630,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":289634,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1908b"},"rt":21451,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":311194,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1908c"},"rt":28762,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":340066,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1908d"},"rt":10994,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":351169,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1908e"},"rt":105596,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":456875,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"C B F Z M F Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1908f"},"rt":9754,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466933,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19090"},"rt":6276,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":473321,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19091"},"rt":17363,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":490798,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19092"},"rt":43515,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":534425,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM03 PMO 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19093"},"rt":16108,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":550645,"subject":"S4T2X","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40025","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.583333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190a4"},"rt":57080,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":129459,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190a5"},"rt":37488,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":167058,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"8H D H H H D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190a6"},"rt":32128,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199294,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190a7"},"rt":65784,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":265199,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"K F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190a8"},"rt":28997,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":294508,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190aa"},"rt":32722,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":333024,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"989A A E E E G G 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190ab"},"rt":54473,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":387600,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.166666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190ac"},"rt":29067,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416772,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190ad"},"rt":14857,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":431729,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190ae"},"rt":18601,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":450435,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190af"},"rt":12606,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":463142,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190b0"},"rt":4812,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":468059,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190b1"},"rt":30530,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":498686,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"M O Z C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190b2"},"rt":22603,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":521391,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"Z H 03 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190b3"},"rt":60282,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":581780,"subject":"ZDA7B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35361","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.583333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,I","hovered":"M X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190d0"},"rt":46314,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":204668,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMA A A A A 10 AM11 AMF F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190d1"},"rt":10820,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":215612,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190d2"},"rt":20121,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":235867,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C 09 AMC C C C 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190d3"},"rt":120613,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":356574,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"F F F K K K 12 PMK K K F F F 11 AMK K K F 09 AM10 AMA A H H I C J H H K F F K K 01 PM01 PMU B D K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190d4"},"rt":201729,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":558583,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"I O A F 7O O O C C C I O A H A 10 AMC C 09 AMC C A A H K I I 2C 09 AMC C 11 AMG I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190d6"},"rt":11620,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":577884,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190d7"},"rt":44213,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":622194,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"J J J I I C H F X X O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190d8"},"rt":139754,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":762046,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"B X X O A A A G G G G G G F F F J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190d9"},"rt":31025,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":793697,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J J I I I 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190da"},"rt":87640,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":881540,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F J J J J J E E E E B B 11 AM12 PM01 PMM B B E 02 PM02 PMX X X C C C O O O O O O Z Z 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190db"},"rt":10669,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":892540,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"11 AMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190dc"},"rt":6744,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":899850,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190dd"},"rt":38994,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":938945,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"09 AM12 PMZ 504 PMN Z I I I J A F B F 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190de"},"rt":63375,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1002413,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PM03 PMI I I I I I I I E E E J J F B B M G C C X X X X X X X O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190df"},"rt":221696,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1224396,"subject":"NDBCA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.416666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,K","hovered":"I J J F F B B M M M 12 PMM M C C C O O A A A E E J J B B F G G G F F F G C C C O M M B B B F G F F F F F G A A K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190f6"},"rt":13045,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":66601,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190f7"},"rt":9786,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":76502,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"K U G D E 04 PM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190f8"},"rt":40624,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":117235,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,U,B","hovered":"C C C C A A A A Z C A A A C C A A A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190f9"},"rt":29013,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":146364,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PM04 PM05 PM05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190fa"},"rt":17116,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":163604,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O I I I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190fc"},"rt":9256,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":174934,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"10 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190fd"},"rt":38442,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213491,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.583333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"J I C H H C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190fe"},"rt":41859,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":255473,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.166666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"9C X X B B I J G C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f190ff"},"rt":16888,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":272479,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5B B J J E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19100"},"rt":7151,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279744,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19101"},"rt":11635,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291501,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19102"},"rt":7111,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":298737,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19103"},"rt":56630,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":355487,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.583333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19104"},"rt":24983,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":380592,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PMO O 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19105"},"rt":49390,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":430106,"subject":"WZFMC","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.25,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,J,N,X","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PMC C C M M X X M C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19116"},"rt":46571,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":124471,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19117"},"rt":13487,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":138060,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"D 8D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19118"},"rt":36850,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":175011,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"Z C C C C C C 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19119"},"rt":16101,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":191214,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.916666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,B","hovered":"F 04 PM04 PM04 PMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1911a"},"rt":36092,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":227614,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.833333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,F,G","hovered":"U U I I I 12 PMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1911c"},"rt":9013,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":241617,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1911d"},"rt":49908,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291625,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.916666666666667,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M,O,X","hovered":"I I M J J J O O O X X X O O O O X M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1911e"},"rt":126887,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":418610,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.16666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":"B B B M B L B I I I J C O H H B B 12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM12 PMB B B B B B 01 PMM M B B E F X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1911f"},"rt":23319,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":442194,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"F J I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19120"},"rt":25308,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467593,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F F F G F F F Z O B B F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19121"},"rt":13135,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":480893,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19122"},"rt":10211,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491205,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"8F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19123"},"rt":41418,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":532720,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L,P","hovered":"7Z N N Z Z L H H H H H L P Z Z H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19124"},"rt":10507,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":543324,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"04 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19125"},"rt":17997,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":561423,"subject":"HV8ZE","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"Z Z 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19136"},"rt":6692,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":41044,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19137"},"rt":11759,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":52977,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"C 09 AM11 AMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19138"},"rt":15598,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":68720,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19139"},"rt":11765,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":80592,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"09 AMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1913a"},"rt":18860,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":99604,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"4O O I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1913c"},"rt":7850,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":114596,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1913d"},"rt":21205,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":135960,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C M 01 PM01 PMX X X X C B F B N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1913e"},"rt":43869,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":179999,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"F B X M J D 01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1913f"},"rt":15439,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":195601,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19140"},"rt":8426,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":204188,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19141"},"rt":9453,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213806,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19142"},"rt":7641,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":221609,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19143"},"rt":13739,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":235505,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"B N Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19144"},"rt":7857,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":243514,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19145"},"rt":9778,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253448,"subject":"FPSQJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"3J X C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19156"},"rt":12789,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":81619,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM11 AMA A 1C C 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19157"},"rt":7196,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":88935,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H D D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19158"},"rt":9276,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":98317,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19159"},"rt":6729,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":105144,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.166666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1915a"},"rt":15001,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":120256,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O K I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1915c"},"rt":27834,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":152914,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I G E 6E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1915d"},"rt":24384,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":177405,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1915e"},"rt":32909,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":210422,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"8F F F B B B E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1915f"},"rt":13886,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":224610,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19160"},"rt":28688,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253402,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"G G F B B B F F F X X X M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19161"},"rt":7035,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":260541,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19162"},"rt":17888,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278525,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B B B B F F 5F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19163"},"rt":20624,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":299248,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"M C H H Z Z Z Z Z Z X F O X I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19164"},"rt":8281,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":307629,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"02 PM03 PMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19165"},"rt":53766,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361496,"subject":"4YF1J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42720","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M M M M B B B B F F G F E I 03 PM02 PMO G G F F F F B 12 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19176"},"rt":28383,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":130015,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM08 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19177"},"rt":21853,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":152102,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"D D G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19178"},"rt":55635,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":208000,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19179"},"rt":17764,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":226042,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"06 PMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1917a"},"rt":51313,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":277613,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I I I 03 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1917c"},"rt":86118,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":369147,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1917d"},"rt":54983,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424541,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1917e"},"rt":111957,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":536710,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.75,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,G,P","hovered":"12 PM4J J 11 AMJ A A 0I E E E E E J J A A A F G G G 10 AM10 AMB B F F B B C C C E C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1917f"},"rt":35099,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":572347,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19180"},"rt":24066,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":596685,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B M 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19181"},"rt":28466,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":625356,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,L,M","hovered":"10 AM01 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19182"},"rt":30533,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":656082,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19183"},"rt":12111,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":668549,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19184"},"rt":12064,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":680837,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PMX X X I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19185"},"rt":39600,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":720598,"subject":"E0F55","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38348","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19196"},"rt":25377,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":137363,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"04 PM12 PM10 AM11 AMF 11 AMF 12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19197"},"rt":13839,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":151302,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"5K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19198"},"rt":9341,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":160745,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19199"},"rt":19163,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":180014,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1919a"},"rt":159153,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":339276,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.916666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,A","hovered":"I I 08 AMI I I 08 AM08 AMI I I O O O 08 AM08 AMI A C 08 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PMA A 08 AMI 08 AMC C A A A 12 PMC 09 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1919c"},"rt":11356,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":353823,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1919d"},"rt":32658,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386595,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C H H C F X X 10 AMX X 02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1919e"},"rt":64513,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":451213,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"I B B B J J I J F X E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1919f"},"rt":34664,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":486145,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I I I I I E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191a0"},"rt":9695,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":495941,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191a1"},"rt":14385,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":510437,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"J M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191a2"},"rt":11990,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":522543,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F G F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191a3"},"rt":29554,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":552197,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"C Z Z Z Z Z 02 PMZ Z Z Z Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191a4"},"rt":8675,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":560978,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191a5"},"rt":167096,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":728179,"subject":"P189K","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36446","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PMB F M 02 PMC 02 PML C 4F C C J M A M J J M C C 02 PMX X X 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191b6"},"rt":105075,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":281175,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A H 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191b7"},"rt":40470,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":322110,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"U U 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191b8"},"rt":10697,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":332971,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C 12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191b9"},"rt":11788,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":344919,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191ba"},"rt":106120,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":451186,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I 11 AM11 AMO O A H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191bc"},"rt":48095,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":510058,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"02 PM09 AMJ J J B B O O X C C G E E G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191bd"},"rt":61246,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":571405,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"5F F B I F F F X O B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191be"},"rt":61667,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":633395,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"B B B B 12 PMB 03 PMO 04 PMD D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191bf"},"rt":19988,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":653724,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"G G J 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191c0"},"rt":13785,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":667667,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"02 PMF 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191c1"},"rt":11735,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":679564,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191c2"},"rt":9508,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":689223,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191c3"},"rt":16544,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":705914,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M Z 02 PMZ F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191c4"},"rt":9689,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":715755,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191c5"},"rt":36740,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":752657,"subject":"86P6B","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34144","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X X X K X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191e2"},"rt":32297,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":86840,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM011 AMC A A A A 2A C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191e3"},"rt":9417,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96429,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z E D E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191e4"},"rt":12311,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":108935,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191e5"},"rt":41633,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":150751,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"02 PMU 04 PMH H A A 604 PM05 PM04 PMU 01 PMU 03 PMZ 04 PMA 12 PMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191e6"},"rt":88689,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":239619,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I 10 AMF C 09 AMF F 0U U 03 PMU U 02 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AMU O I I I O O 11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191e8"},"rt":8075,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":250669,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191e9"},"rt":25605,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":276374,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E O O X X H X X B B F F F B B B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191ea"},"rt":43607,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":320083,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"7B B I I I I J J F F 03 PMC C G G E 02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191eb"},"rt":30438,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":351587,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I I G J J I J J J J J I I J B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191ec"},"rt":25496,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377329,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F 02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMB B F F F 02 PM02 PMB B F B B B F X X Z C 03 PM04 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191ed"},"rt":7231,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":385035,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191ee"},"rt":5667,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":390866,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B B B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191ef"},"rt":51143,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":442173,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.166666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"B J B Z 02 PM02 PM02 PM04 PM02 PMZ 04 PMZ 5Z 04 PMZ Z Z 04 PM04 PM03 PMC O O G X X 01 PM04 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191f0"},"rt":31443,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":474072,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.916666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,X","hovered":"F 03 PM03 PM03 PMX 504 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM01 PM12 PME I E E E X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f191f1"},"rt":84704,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":558940,"subject":"94FR9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38102","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"004 PM03 PM02 PM02 PMX X X B 02 PM02 PM02 PM02 PMX 03 PMM 01 PMO O F G 5O O B B B B 02 PMX O O Z M D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19202"},"rt":17502,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":77512,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19203"},"rt":16376,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":93996,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3A K I F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19204"},"rt":6892,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100986,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19205"},"rt":50172,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":151256,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X,K","hovered":"02 PM01 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19206"},"rt":16890,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":168343,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19208"},"rt":46975,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":221496,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19209"},"rt":116209,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":337804,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1920a"},"rt":55352,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":393786,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1920b"},"rt":22067,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":415955,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1920c"},"rt":7223,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":423283,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1920d"},"rt":20877,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":444258,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1920e"},"rt":56072,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":500437,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1920f"},"rt":72771,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":573313,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19210"},"rt":15061,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":588730,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19211"},"rt":14573,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":603399,"subject":"7FU37","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35316","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19222"},"rt":61510,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":166231,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AMO 11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19223"},"rt":7718,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":174331,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"1K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19224"},"rt":12057,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":186484,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM11 AMF C C 11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19225"},"rt":7266,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":193849,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19226"},"rt":16521,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":210466,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19228"},"rt":7554,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":229283,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19229"},"rt":33785,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":263165,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"3F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1922a"},"rt":44945,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":308216,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"C B B B 708 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1922b"},"rt":36724,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":345038,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1922c"},"rt":29513,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":374651,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J 02 PM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1922d"},"rt":12626,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":387384,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"302 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1922e"},"rt":15208,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402688,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B F F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1922f"},"rt":20428,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":423213,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X O I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19230"},"rt":13577,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":436889,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19231"},"rt":20648,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":457717,"subject":"BDQEZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19242"},"rt":23583,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":77625,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"3O 11 AMF A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19243"},"rt":6086,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":83838,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19244"},"rt":22599,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":106561,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A 01 PM12 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19245"},"rt":48797,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":155483,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"04 PMB O 05 PM05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19246"},"rt":170420,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":326021,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I G G 01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AMI I I I 02 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19248"},"rt":6277,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":335478,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19249"},"rt":68011,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":403599,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"4O O X X B B B B F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1924a"},"rt":24107,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427981,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G G B B G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1924b"},"rt":36615,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":464701,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B B J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1924c"},"rt":8390,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":473207,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1924d"},"rt":7803,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":481134,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"10 AM01 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1924e"},"rt":9960,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491218,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"L L F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1924f"},"rt":15230,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":506570,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"P Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19250"},"rt":11604,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":518300,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19251"},"rt":13957,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":532351,"subject":"KGNC3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41808","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"B 03 PM02 PM02 PMX X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19262"},"rt":51312,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":132900,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"F C F F O F A 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19263"},"rt":38319,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":171331,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"A F 12 PMZ D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19264"},"rt":28028,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199470,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,H","hovered":"008 AMC A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19265"},"rt":20705,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":220301,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"H 04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMD D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19266"},"rt":81650,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":302064,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":11,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,I,X,C,J,A,H,F,K,D,U,E,Z","hovered":"F I 12 PM11 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19268"},"rt":9185,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":318246,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19269"},"rt":27665,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346024,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"B X O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1926a"},"rt":54573,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":400712,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F,G","hovered":"B B G G B B B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1926b"},"rt":44948,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":445769,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"N B B 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1926c"},"rt":26573,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":472451,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H H C G B F 02 PM02 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1926d"},"rt":9671,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":482233,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1926e"},"rt":9344,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491686,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1926f"},"rt":14207,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":506008,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19270"},"rt":10140,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":516257,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PM04 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19271"},"rt":17157,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":533525,"subject":"5QAJA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43033","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19282"},"rt":12970,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":105744,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"2C A Z Z 01 PM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19283"},"rt":16968,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":122810,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C Z K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19284"},"rt":16108,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139013,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A A C C 10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19285"},"rt":23599,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":162701,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19286"},"rt":190377,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":353167,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C U F F Z 12 PMA A O 12 PM12 PM12 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19288"},"rt":14717,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":376586,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19289"},"rt":26014,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402687,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"2B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1928a"},"rt":42277,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445053,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H 04 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1928b"},"rt":39115,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":484255,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J X M 10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1928c"},"rt":29504,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":513852,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F 03 PM04 PMM X X M 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1928d"},"rt":10323,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":524269,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1928e"},"rt":7965,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":532323,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1928f"},"rt":40535,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":572968,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"04 PM04 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMM 01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19290"},"rt":34420,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":607480,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"3X 04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM10 AM01 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19291"},"rt":32173,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":639742,"subject":"V9JKJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29574","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192a2"},"rt":43676,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":117364,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM12 PM12 PMO 11 AMC 11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192a3"},"rt":531518,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":648974,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D 04 PMZ D D D 62408 AMD G G 08 AMO O O 11 AM11 AMO 11 AMC O C C C C H 01 PM09 AM07 PM04 PMA 10 AM08 AMO 03 PM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM05 PM12 PM11 AMA Z 04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMF F F Z Z K K D E U E E 03 PM03 PMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192a4"},"rt":13828,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":663085,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192a5"},"rt":9776,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":672960,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192a6"},"rt":14441,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":687610,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192a8"},"rt":9447,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":703709,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM66E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192a9"},"rt":37760,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":741563,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I F B B B B M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192aa"},"rt":106617,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":848277,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"5C C B B 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192ab"},"rt":99241,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":947798,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I J J 11 AM10 AMB I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192ac"},"rt":16048,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":964111,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192ad"},"rt":10040,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":974247,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"2M M L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192ae"},"rt":15226,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":989884,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B F F 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192af"},"rt":25011,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1014990,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"C C O B F Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192b0"},"rt":15979,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1031061,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192b1"},"rt":13006,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1044161,"subject":"6HUZT","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"I 02 PM02 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192c2"},"rt":108212,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":158643,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM01 PM01 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192c3"},"rt":88452,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":247506,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"10D 04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM11 AM10 AM06 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AMA 10 AM12 PMA 12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192c4"},"rt":29655,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":277641,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"3C 12 PMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192c5"},"rt":9684,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":287415,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192c6"},"rt":15332,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":302840,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I I 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192c8"},"rt":7549,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":317431,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192c9"},"rt":92158,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":409691,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M,X","hovered":"F O F C Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192ca"},"rt":111539,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":521489,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,G,K","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192cb"},"rt":54132,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":575855,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192cc"},"rt":29119,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":605065,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192cd"},"rt":103018,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":708178,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM12 PMM M M 12 PM02 PMC 01 PM01 PM12 PMM 12 PM10 AMB 01 PM12 PMM M M 01 PM01 PM12 PM01 PMM M 01 PM01 PM12 PM01 PML H H 03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMH H L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192ce"},"rt":46236,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":754651,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"2F F F B B 12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AMH L L K X X 02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192cf"},"rt":40103,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":794842,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192d0"},"rt":36310,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":831237,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192d1"},"rt":9000,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":840326,"subject":"X7HS7","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192ee"},"rt":8621,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":77324,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192ef"},"rt":9206,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":86707,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"09 AM10 AM12 PME E D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192f0"},"rt":9595,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96507,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"10 AMC A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192f1"},"rt":28364,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":124974,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"104 PM04 PMU U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192f2"},"rt":33513,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":158576,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192f4"},"rt":8602,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":173741,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192f5"},"rt":11033,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":184957,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192f6"},"rt":26242,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":211290,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192f7"},"rt":17852,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":229257,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192f8"},"rt":7073,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":236493,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192f9"},"rt":8744,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":245345,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192fa"},"rt":4555,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":249996,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192fb"},"rt":5272,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":255363,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192fc"},"rt":1950,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257413,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f192fd"},"rt":7381,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":264897,"subject":"YWPBP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40787","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1930e"},"rt":18938,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":127386,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1930f"},"rt":11622,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139118,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I X D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19310"},"rt":70777,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":210001,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"2C C C C C A B 12 PM12 PMZ C C C C U A A 09 AMC A 08 AM09 AMC 11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19311"},"rt":16558,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":226869,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19312"},"rt":19559,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":246535,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"10I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19314"},"rt":7861,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":260989,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"7E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19315"},"rt":23287,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":284384,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C C F J J O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19316"},"rt":44705,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329201,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B E F 02 PM01 PM12 PM09 AM9O F B B B I I F G G G O N N Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19317"},"rt":71484,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":400800,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I","hovered":"9G J I 12 PMB B B B I I I 11 AMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19318"},"rt":7636,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":408750,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19319"},"rt":11584,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":420451,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"009 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1931a"},"rt":8176,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":428733,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"10 AM10 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1931b"},"rt":10930,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":439769,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"K Z B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1931c"},"rt":12752,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452633,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"09 AME 04 PMX X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1931d"},"rt":10473,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":463783,"subject":"UN7PD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1932e"},"rt":11209,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":48720,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1932f"},"rt":9525,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58359,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F 01 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19330"},"rt":28030,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":86495,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.33333333333333337,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":8,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X,O,I,J,H,F,K,E,G","hovered":"C A A C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19331"},"rt":5818,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":92423,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19332"},"rt":7393,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":99923,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19334"},"rt":8056,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":110005,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19335"},"rt":2768,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":112878,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19336"},"rt":698,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":113685,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19337"},"rt":638,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":114429,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19338"},"rt":628,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":115167,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19339"},"rt":551,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":115845,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1933a"},"rt":1434,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":117413,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1933b"},"rt":593,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":118150,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1933c"},"rt":583,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118843,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1933d"},"rt":4045,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122998,"subject":"6RQTQ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36629","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1934e"},"rt":47798,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":115005,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"01 PM01 PMX X 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1934f"},"rt":16193,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":131300,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19350"},"rt":7798,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139197,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19351"},"rt":63877,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":203164,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PMU U 04 PM04 PMU U 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19352"},"rt":42596,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":246012,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"O I O O 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PMU U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19354"},"rt":9923,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":258831,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19355"},"rt":12193,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271116,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19356"},"rt":54907,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":326116,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B L 6E I J J J X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19357"},"rt":22830,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":349036,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"O B B 12 PM12 PMJ J J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19358"},"rt":57196,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406324,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F B Z Z F X X X I X F F F F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19359"},"rt":6284,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":412701,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1935a"},"rt":3234,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416132,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1935b"},"rt":9797,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":426021,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1935c"},"rt":19381,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445492,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"04 PM03 PMB B B 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1935d"},"rt":9425,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":455012,"subject":"G5HED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1936e"},"rt":25048,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94838,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"U F 78101110 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM611 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AMA A 10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1936f"},"rt":8395,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":103346,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5O E E E Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19370"},"rt":36930,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":140687,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"H H A C C C Z Z Z 12 PMC C 12 PM12 PMZ Z C A C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19371"},"rt":49176,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":189965,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PMC C F U 04 PMH H H 04 PMH H 03 PM04 PMU 04 PM04 PME E 04 PME E E E D 04 PM04 PM02 PMU U B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19372"},"rt":74351,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":264421,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I J D Z H H O 11 AM11 AMI 12 PMA 03 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19374"},"rt":8577,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":277757,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19375"},"rt":10968,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":288820,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F F Z B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19376"},"rt":25853,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":314785,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F E E G H F F B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19377"},"rt":12541,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":327429,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"3J I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19378"},"rt":33554,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361082,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"O X F B B O 04 PM04 PMX 06 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19379"},"rt":6204,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367383,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1937a"},"rt":5776,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":373490,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1937b"},"rt":54624,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":428209,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"B Z 04 PMZ Z Z F O Z 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1937c"},"rt":20504,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448818,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1937d"},"rt":32732,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":481648,"subject":"SKPWA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38985","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX X H H O 03 PM02 PMX X X X X K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19394"},"rt":12835,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":302811,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19395"},"rt":11399,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":314332,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19396"},"rt":11624,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":326067,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19397"},"rt":17229,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":343627,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19398"},"rt":19373,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":363095,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1939a"},"rt":2547,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":367625,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1939b"},"rt":2028,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369752,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1939c"},"rt":1442,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":371293,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1939d"},"rt":2449,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":373904,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1939e"},"rt":1421,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375461,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1939f"},"rt":230,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375895,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193a0"},"rt":2057,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":378095,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193a1"},"rt":1847,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":380055,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193a2"},"rt":1483,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":381750,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193a3"},"rt":1396,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":383340,"subject":"ZCMED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36561","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193c0"},"rt":47317,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1810343,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"U F 10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AMA Z A A 11 AM11 AMA A A 11 AMA C C C C 10 AMC C 10 AM10 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193c1"},"rt":24295,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1834777,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"12 PMU Z B G G K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193c2"},"rt":17214,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1852143,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AMC C C 10 AM10 AM12 PMZ Z Z Z 12 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193c3"},"rt":42336,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1894624,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"A 12 PMC C 03 PM04 PMK H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193c4"},"rt":12695,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1907472,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O I I 04 PMI O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193c6"},"rt":14068,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1938072,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"3E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193c7"},"rt":39170,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1977344,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"J J J J C O N J J 11 AM11 AM11 AMO X X I N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193c8"},"rt":40859,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2018348,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F,I,J","hovered":"7L L L B B F 11 AMI G I G F G G F B I E F 03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193c9"},"rt":20977,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2039489,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E F 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193ca"},"rt":10209,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2049860,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193cb"},"rt":10481,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2060493,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193cc"},"rt":11687,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2072335,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193cd"},"rt":29568,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2102010,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"01 PM01 PMZ L C M M Z 02 PMZ Z Z 06 PMZ 08 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193ce"},"rt":11013,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2113180,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"C 12 PM02 PMX 03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193cf"},"rt":12037,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2125323,"subject":"76UV0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42306","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"403 PM02 PMX X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193e0"},"rt":82138,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":207157,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMA 61F F Z F F O C C F F F 02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193e1"},"rt":40809,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":248208,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"F D K D D D D D U D K D D K F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193e2"},"rt":11306,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":259598,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"U A C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193e3"},"rt":7963,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":267649,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"O 04 PMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193e4"},"rt":13688,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":281420,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"3J I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193e6"},"rt":11714,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":303018,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"986E G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193e7"},"rt":28162,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":331267,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"12111096O X X X X X M M B B B Z 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193e8"},"rt":94325,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":425678,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"8E E G B G G O X 6C H O X X D C C G B B G C C C C C C C C G F F O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193e9"},"rt":51558,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":477531,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J E E E E J 5F G B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193ea"},"rt":9930,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":487543,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O O O F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193eb"},"rt":9235,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":496861,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM02 PM12 PMM M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193ec"},"rt":13713,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":510660,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"X O F F F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193ed"},"rt":15018,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":525780,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193ee"},"rt":12480,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":538394,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"C C X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f193ef"},"rt":12457,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":550943,"subject":"T8OB0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42192","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19406"},"rt":38809,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109054,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19407"},"rt":10647,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":119809,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19408"},"rt":53555,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173478,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,U,B","hovered":"H C A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19409"},"rt":13080,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":186670,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1940a"},"rt":61336,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":248224,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,K","hovered":"I I I I I O O O O I I O I I O O O O F I 12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1940c"},"rt":7121,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":261254,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1940d"},"rt":34787,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296158,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C C B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1940e"},"rt":37407,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":333669,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B I B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1940f"},"rt":22266,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":356035,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,O","hovered":"J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19410"},"rt":10159,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":366298,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19411"},"rt":7866,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":374270,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19412"},"rt":5564,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":379937,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19413"},"rt":47583,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":427623,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,P","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19414"},"rt":31571,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":459297,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"J 03 PM11 AM03 PMG E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19415"},"rt":22610,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":482021,"subject":"04YXZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"27149","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"X X C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19426"},"rt":12209,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":123002,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"6O 11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19427"},"rt":9317,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":132428,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19428"},"rt":31498,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":164057,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A C C A A C C A C 10 AMC A C A Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19429"},"rt":18324,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":182492,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"05 PM04 PMZ Z U U G B B B K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1942a"},"rt":51009,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":233604,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,K","hovered":"J O I 6A A C C C A C C C A I I I I I I I I I H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1942c"},"rt":5802,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":242035,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1942d"},"rt":18116,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":260268,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C C F F B B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1942e"},"rt":34326,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294860,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"Z X N C F F F B F J J J E E E E J J J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1942f"},"rt":14899,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":309870,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19430"},"rt":34687,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344669,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"D N F B F F F Z Z X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19431"},"rt":7466,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352243,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M 01 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19432"},"rt":7986,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":360347,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19433"},"rt":34993,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":395446,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O G F J H Z Z Z Z 04 PM04 PMZ Z Z F B B B O O O X B O Z Z F C Z C C C H G E E G F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19434"},"rt":30479,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":426044,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"X 04 PM03 PMO X B B B B O O M M M M M X X J B F F C K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19435"},"rt":19410,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445563,"subject":"YV1XZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,K","hovered":"02 PMX X 8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19446"},"rt":29253,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":64919,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A 6C 11 AM12 PMC A A A O O I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19447"},"rt":25422,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":90465,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5O U H D D E E 04 PME D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19448"},"rt":39812,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":130393,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C 10 AMC C 11 AM11 AM12 PMZ 12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19449"},"rt":43076,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173590,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"Z 312 PMC E O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1944a"},"rt":4809,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":178524,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,K,U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1944c"},"rt":6155,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":188844,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F,I,L","hovered":"2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1944d"},"rt":4723,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":193694,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.6666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,C,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1944e"},"rt":4444,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198262,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.75,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,M,N,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1944f"},"rt":3813,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":202201,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,H,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19450"},"rt":7682,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":210004,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,I,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19451"},"rt":4773,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":215071,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,K,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19452"},"rt":4567,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":219778,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,J,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19453"},"rt":4436,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":224700,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,N,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19454"},"rt":4875,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229729,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,H,O,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19455"},"rt":4853,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234716,"subject":"G6248","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40863","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,H,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19466"},"rt":127760,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":259288,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMO C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19467"},"rt":57581,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":317235,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19468"},"rt":56290,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":373661,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3C C C 10 AM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19469"},"rt":108084,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":481875,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"01 PM01 PMZ Z F A F 01 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1946a"},"rt":89046,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":571272,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"I A A 12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1946c"},"rt":20625,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":602928,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1946d"},"rt":26446,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":629510,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1946e"},"rt":39403,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":669035,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1946f"},"rt":40962,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":710135,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"65"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19470"},"rt":73299,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":783578,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19471"},"rt":19064,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":803015,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19472"},"rt":17818,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":820968,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19473"},"rt":39275,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":860374,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19474"},"rt":35621,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":896153,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"12 PME 03 PM02 PM1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19475"},"rt":51600,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":947886,"subject":"G1GGZ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PME E E 11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19486"},"rt":32262,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94229,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"012 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19487"},"rt":12287,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":106707,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"4C K D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19488"},"rt":22471,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":129471,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"5A C 10 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19489"},"rt":45810,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":175690,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PMK A C O A A A Z Z U U Z Z H H H K U Z A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1948a"},"rt":90569,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":266831,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I A I I I 03 PM02 PM03 PMU U Z Z F F I A A A A I H A A F O H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1948c"},"rt":8583,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":278504,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1948d"},"rt":29968,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":308587,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"G C F F B B B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1948e"},"rt":32164,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":340971,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1948f"},"rt":15579,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":356660,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19490"},"rt":29431,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386199,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19491"},"rt":6749,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":393245,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19492"},"rt":8359,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":401800,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19493"},"rt":27207,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":429117,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19494"},"rt":40222,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469535,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19495"},"rt":27285,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":496934,"subject":"UJFX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"30653","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194ac"},"rt":72598,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":162067,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"11 AM11 AM6510 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM08 AM09 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM508 AM09 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM1008 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194ad"},"rt":60563,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":222976,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"12 PM12 PMZ 04 PM04 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM08 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM12 PM11 AM10 AMO 11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM11 AMX J 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194ae"},"rt":140175,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":363481,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"501 PM12 PMC 10 AM10 AM10 AMC C C C C C C 10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM10 AMC 12 PM12 PM01 PMZ Z F 04 PM03 PM05 PM04 PMC 0C C C 10 AMC 12 PM12 PM12 PMA A Z Z Z Z Z U B B B B G G D D D E 111 AM12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AMC C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194af"},"rt":41160,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":404974,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"304 PM7A F 04 PM05 PMG G 05 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM01 PMH H Z Z 12 PM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194b0"},"rt":17427,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":422499,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"H I I 11 AMI I I I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194b2"},"rt":11609,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":440686,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194b3"},"rt":28587,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469371,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F B B B B B B B B B B B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194b4"},"rt":36418,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":505880,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E B B X X B B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194b5"},"rt":22577,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":528545,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"F J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194b6"},"rt":8395,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":537032,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O M B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194b7"},"rt":6774,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":543900,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"6M 12 PM12 PMF 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194b8"},"rt":5754,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":549750,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194b9"},"rt":33583,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":583429,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z 04 PM04 PMZ O O 03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM03 PM02 PMX 01 PMM 12 PMB B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194ba"},"rt":26357,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":609878,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"6J J 12 PM11 AM10 AM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194bb"},"rt":93771,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":703740,"subject":"2KS3T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42915","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"07 PM05 PM04 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PMM M 01 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM02 PMM M M M 02 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM10 AMJ 11 AM10 AM408 AM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM33"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194cc"},"rt":52798,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96839,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194cd"},"rt":7035,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":103978,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194ce"},"rt":19668,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":123748,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194cf"},"rt":26147,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":149999,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"G G G K H U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194d0"},"rt":5335,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":155440,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194d2"},"rt":8629,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":167387,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194d3"},"rt":28613,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":196106,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F F F F 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194d4"},"rt":31222,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":227432,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O X X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194d5"},"rt":3865,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":231397,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194d6"},"rt":34344,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265842,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194d7"},"rt":7833,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":273772,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J J M M B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194d8"},"rt":7748,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281616,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"8F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194d9"},"rt":35676,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":317393,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194da"},"rt":2094,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":319588,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194db"},"rt":2259,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321954,"subject":"8C6B0","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41662","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194ec"},"rt":8485,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":22039,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM12 PM11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194ed"},"rt":9932,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":32081,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194ee"},"rt":12933,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":45134,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194ef"},"rt":5826,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":51180,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194f0"},"rt":7195,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58473,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194f2"},"rt":9197,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":68446,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194f3"},"rt":17032,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":85601,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194f4"},"rt":30081,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":115782,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"I B B F F F F F F O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194f5"},"rt":15669,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":131553,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B M I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194f6"},"rt":13460,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":145112,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194f7"},"rt":9895,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":155105,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194f8"},"rt":6871,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162714,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194f9"},"rt":11483,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":174354,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194fa"},"rt":6912,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":181407,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f194fb"},"rt":17348,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198890,"subject":"7OYPU","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"10 AM11 AM02 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1950c"},"rt":33291,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100266,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,A","hovered":"12 PM11 AM11 AMA O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1950d"},"rt":38578,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":138972,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G,B","hovered":"F D J G 04 PMG B B B E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1950e"},"rt":40442,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":179541,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,I,A","hovered":"C 10 AMC A F O F F A F A F A F C C F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1950f"},"rt":89255,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":268922,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,F","hovered":"303 PM04 PMD 04 PM04 PMK F 10 AM10 AMA A I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19510"},"rt":88595,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":357836,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,U","hovered":"I 12 PMA I I U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19512"},"rt":41729,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":406143,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I G G M M B G X X C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19513"},"rt":26300,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":432576,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M 12 PM12 PMF F F G G I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19514"},"rt":48108,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":480812,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19515"},"rt":116029,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":596969,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"4B J J F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19516"},"rt":50706,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":647995,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"10 AM11 AMF F B 05 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19517"},"rt":10887,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":659063,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AM11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19518"},"rt":9396,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":668600,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19519"},"rt":24623,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":693344,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"05 PM05 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1951a"},"rt":31812,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":725280,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1951b"},"rt":122047,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":847506,"subject":"PVRS1","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42016","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E","hovered":"12 PM02 PM28C E I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1952c"},"rt":12223,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58056,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1952d"},"rt":8927,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":67101,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"36"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1952e"},"rt":105131,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":172355,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"C C C C O O O O J J D D 02 PM03 PMC C A B B A C C C O O J J 11 AM11 AM142C C O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1952f"},"rt":11637,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":184334,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"04 PM04 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19530"},"rt":22027,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":206472,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X,U","hovered":"I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19532"},"rt":35206,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":243395,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"G E E E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19533"},"rt":43979,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":287506,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19534"},"rt":33377,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321074,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19535"},"rt":13769,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":335054,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19536"},"rt":50943,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386107,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F P C G C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19537"},"rt":8118,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":394335,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"402 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19538"},"rt":4886,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":399369,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19539"},"rt":18062,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":417557,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1953a"},"rt":10512,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":428178,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1953b"},"rt":36344,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":464632,"subject":"E7S9U","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29870","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,G","hovered":"02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19558"},"rt":27849,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":63700,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19559"},"rt":15546,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":79346,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"H D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1955a"},"rt":24607,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":104046,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,A","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1955b"},"rt":41499,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":145637,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"03 PM03 PM04 PMA F A A A O O U H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1955c"},"rt":50765,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":196496,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I I I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1955e"},"rt":9370,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":208942,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1955f"},"rt":20350,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229395,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19560"},"rt":29288,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258776,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19561"},"rt":12347,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":271228,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19562"},"rt":14106,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285429,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F 04 PMO M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19563"},"rt":5936,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291462,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19564"},"rt":4097,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":295661,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19565"},"rt":25732,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":321502,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z 2X Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19566"},"rt":11690,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":333287,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19567"},"rt":23908,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":357295,"subject":"5FMKD","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42878","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19578"},"rt":49501,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":130868,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"C J J I 76"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19579"},"rt":16053,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":147027,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"O H D D D D G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1957a"},"rt":79336,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":226466,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"K O C C A C 211 AM12 PM12 PMO O K K C B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1957b"},"rt":31045,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":257842,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F H H D D G G F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1957c"},"rt":19523,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":277461,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1957e"},"rt":37917,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":326442,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"3J J J B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1957f"},"rt":22352,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":348894,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19580"},"rt":89623,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438615,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,M","hovered":"6L B B B X X X C B B B X X B B G F B G B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19581"},"rt":42296,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":481238,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J B B J J B J J B B B J I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19582"},"rt":18980,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":500316,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L,P","hovered":"F F H H 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19583"},"rt":7436,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":507855,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M M B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19584"},"rt":7722,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515677,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19585"},"rt":46092,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":561868,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"O Z Z F F F Z Z F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19586"},"rt":38609,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":600588,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"G B J I B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19587"},"rt":61519,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":662207,"subject":"ZMRMB","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29101","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"X X X J I K K M 01 PMM X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19598"},"rt":18551,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":36977,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19599"},"rt":13907,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":50992,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C U Z D 04 PMD D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1959a"},"rt":12203,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":63308,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"2F C 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1959b"},"rt":33581,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":97066,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"404 PM03 PMU Z Z Z U U F A O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1959c"},"rt":115273,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":212464,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"10 AM03 PMI 12 PM12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1959e"},"rt":11309,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":230642,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"5E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1959f"},"rt":20559,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":251537,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"44"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195a0"},"rt":44818,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296492,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E B B B E E I 02 PMX E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195a1"},"rt":25879,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":322516,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195a2"},"rt":17799,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":340444,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"X B B B B Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195a3"},"rt":12539,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":353149,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"X B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195a4"},"rt":7741,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361034,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195a5"},"rt":28572,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":389736,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"B X N M Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195a6"},"rt":21524,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411383,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM03 PMX M B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195a7"},"rt":27162,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438707,"subject":"ML0PA","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41376","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"M 02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195b8"},"rt":22993,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":279013,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195b9"},"rt":11898,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":291013,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195ba"},"rt":15506,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":306626,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195bb"},"rt":88187,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":394922,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"K 04 PM04 PMF O O K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195bc"},"rt":117986,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":513333,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"901 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195be"},"rt":7409,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":529347,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195bf"},"rt":95988,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":625442,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195c0"},"rt":47044,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":672895,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195c1"},"rt":31158,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":704215,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"Z J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195c2"},"rt":35318,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":739635,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F Z Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195c3"},"rt":26663,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":766400,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195c4"},"rt":25349,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":791867,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195c5"},"rt":28622,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":820589,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195c6"},"rt":45454,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":866143,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"04 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMB M O O F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195c7"},"rt":86234,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":952479,"subject":"HOMX9","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40709","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J,M","hovered":"1087612X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195d8"},"rt":12277,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":72682,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195d9"},"rt":15854,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":88686,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AM12 PM01 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195da"},"rt":8077,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96864,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195db"},"rt":38709,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":135676,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"05 PM04 PME 05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195dc"},"rt":17624,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":153458,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"7O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195de"},"rt":10354,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":167273,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195df"},"rt":25501,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":192880,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195e0"},"rt":86297,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279294,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3G C C O B B B B B 12 PM12 PMC B F F B E E 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195e1"},"rt":10203,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":289785,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195e2"},"rt":5500,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":295390,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195e3"},"rt":12747,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":308246,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195e4"},"rt":7099,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":315516,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195e5"},"rt":40778,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":356395,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195e6"},"rt":47272,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":403768,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM08 AM001 PM10 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMA A A G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195e7"},"rt":36892,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":440779,"subject":"JDHT2","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PMX 12 PM12 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195f8"},"rt":32614,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":148606,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"C C C 11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMC C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195f9"},"rt":23483,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":172340,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"A D U 01 PMK 05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195fa"},"rt":9360,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":181836,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM11 AMC 09 AMC C 11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195fb"},"rt":17522,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199474,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"Z 03 PM04 PMH A H H 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195fc"},"rt":19822,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":219441,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I A A 11 AMA A A A A I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195fe"},"rt":12175,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":238940,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM09 AME G 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f195ff"},"rt":41897,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":280997,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I C C C F 03 PMN X 12 PM01 PMX X O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19600"},"rt":49557,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330688,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"L B B B B B F G G G C G G G G C C C G B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19601"},"rt":40185,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":370989,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,I","hovered":"M B B B B B B J J J B B 10 AMF 10 AM10 AME B B B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19602"},"rt":60774,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":432003,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19603"},"rt":8880,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":441356,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"11 AM12 PMM M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19604"},"rt":6814,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448371,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19605"},"rt":21362,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":470138,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"02 PM02 PM02 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19606"},"rt":19843,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":490096,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"J 04 PM04 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19607"},"rt":77764,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":567973,"subject":"WOJNW","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33294","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"I 01 PM02 PMX X X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19618"},"rt":42755,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":70291,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMF F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19619"},"rt":12496,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":82948,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"05 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PMH K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1961a"},"rt":77993,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":161059,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,H","hovered":"C F A 10 AMC C C A A A A A A A A A H H H C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1961b"},"rt":66255,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":227614,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1961c"},"rt":18102,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":246047,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"O O I A A 11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1961e"},"rt":20432,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":269137,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,I,O","hovered":"10 AM11 AM10 AM09 AMJ I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1961f"},"rt":40760,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":310003,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19620"},"rt":92466,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402613,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J B B B B B B X X F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19621"},"rt":60047,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":462995,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"2J M B B J J J B 11 AM10 AM08 AMI J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19622"},"rt":14065,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":477671,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19623"},"rt":8951,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":486723,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19624"},"rt":5491,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":492311,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"4F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19625"},"rt":12533,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":504945,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"O 01 PMZ Z Z N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19626"},"rt":10816,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515857,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19627"},"rt":18616,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":534591,"subject":"SO0DO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40135","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PMZ 02 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19638"},"rt":75904,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199794,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I 11 AM01 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMA I I X X A 11 AM11 AMA A C C A C C A A F O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19639"},"rt":23933,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":224029,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"9D D D E E E E D J H D D E G B E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1963a"},"rt":30067,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":254204,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"5A C C C C C A A Z C C A C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1963b"},"rt":110425,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":364765,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"A C E E E E E E X X X C A A A C C A U B B K X X Z Z F 06 PM05 PM04 PME E 12 PM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1963c"},"rt":50219,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":415264,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I 3C 03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1963e"},"rt":23788,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":444540,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E E E 1066E E E E E G 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1963f"},"rt":29465,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":474090,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I F F B 5J B B F M X O O H Z Z D C C X O Z H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19640"},"rt":51014,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":525199,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A C B B B B F F E G E 7C F B B B B F F E F F J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19641"},"rt":19064,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":544375,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"3F J J J J J J I B B I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19642"},"rt":55624,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":600084,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19643"},"rt":10562,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":610735,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19644"},"rt":8967,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":619796,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19645"},"rt":22622,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":642544,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"3B O Z Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19646"},"rt":37029,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":679677,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"C C B G O 4B 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19647"},"rt":43453,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":723273,"subject":"NEK50","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42978","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"2C X X 5H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19658"},"rt":102681,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":167232,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"11 AMC C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19659"},"rt":124092,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":291558,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"D D D Z 01 PMZ D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1965a"},"rt":9595,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":301409,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"1C C 10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1965b"},"rt":68900,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":370410,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"010 AM11 AM01 PM1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1965c"},"rt":133831,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":504485,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1965e"},"rt":9640,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":519640,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1965f"},"rt":14600,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":534336,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19660"},"rt":56580,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":591018,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"X X 04 PM03 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19661"},"rt":19642,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":610759,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19662"},"rt":97093,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":707945,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19663"},"rt":6463,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":714672,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19664"},"rt":6799,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":721572,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19665"},"rt":20832,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":742505,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19666"},"rt":24751,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":767354,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19667"},"rt":125401,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":892861,"subject":"M3E87","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36525","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19678"},"rt":44615,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":197002,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A 11 AMF F 11 AM08 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19679"},"rt":6395,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":203515,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1967a"},"rt":10801,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":214428,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1967b"},"rt":5628,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":220173,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"06 PM05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1967c"},"rt":8565,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":228868,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1967e"},"rt":8559,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":243882,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1967f"},"rt":15398,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259392,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19680"},"rt":41402,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":300915,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G G G G B B X X F B B B B E X X X X 03 PMO O O O C C C O O C G C C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19681"},"rt":42812,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":343843,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J 09 AMI I I I E I I I I B B B B E E E E E E F B B B B B B B B B B B B B 12 PMJ J J I I 12 PMB J E X 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19682"},"rt":5486,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":349452,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F E 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19683"},"rt":7004,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":356568,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM12 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19684"},"rt":6748,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":363430,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19685"},"rt":7344,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":370888,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19686"},"rt":6057,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377057,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19687"},"rt":11713,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":388878,"subject":"4GC8J","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36207","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19698"},"rt":13199,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":204123,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19699"},"rt":25034,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":229390,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1969a"},"rt":18935,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":248648,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1969b"},"rt":27245,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":276004,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1969c"},"rt":297569,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":573683,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1969e"},"rt":11505,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":593768,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1969f"},"rt":18329,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":612199,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196a0"},"rt":108561,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":720868,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196a1"},"rt":27818,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":748942,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196a2"},"rt":46884,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":795931,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196a3"},"rt":21280,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":817319,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196a4"},"rt":6936,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":824355,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196a5"},"rt":20883,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":845347,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196a6"},"rt":22735,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":868197,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196a7"},"rt":41335,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":909635,"subject":"C2AHN","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"43063","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196b8"},"rt":5266,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":39849,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"2F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196b9"},"rt":10249,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":50355,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196ba"},"rt":22932,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":73483,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,H","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196bb"},"rt":16376,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":90042,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196bc"},"rt":63041,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":153251,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196be"},"rt":8226,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":163829,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"811 AM10 AME G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196bf"},"rt":38871,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202869,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196c0"},"rt":67533,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":270569,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196c1"},"rt":27188,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":298188,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196c2"},"rt":6407,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":304766,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196c3"},"rt":8062,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":312986,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"43"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196c4"},"rt":6427,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":319589,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196c5"},"rt":14565,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":334320,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196c6"},"rt":8253,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342733,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196c7"},"rt":18396,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361288,"subject":"WBJ2T","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196d8"},"rt":58116,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":133966,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM12 PM11 AMA A A 11 AM11 AMA A I I O 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196d9"},"rt":27799,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":161907,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I U A D 04 PM04 PMD J 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196da"},"rt":34157,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":196213,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C C A A A A F F C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196db"},"rt":11999,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":208375,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"J D D D D 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196dc"},"rt":147706,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":356239,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"I I I A A 03 PM03 PMU U Z 01 PM02 PM01 PMZ U U U 02 PM02 PMU C C C 10 AMA A A 12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PMF F 01 PM02 PMO 12 PM01 PM01 PM01 PMU H H Z Z 02 PM03 PM03 PMF H I H I I J H Z 01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMD K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196de"},"rt":11531,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":373381,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196df"},"rt":28665,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402198,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196e0"},"rt":32144,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":434491,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"98E I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196e1"},"rt":26071,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":460712,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196e2"},"rt":89135,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":549991,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"A A F H F F F F F B 12 PMM 02 PMM X 02 PMX 03 PM04 PMX X 4B 04 PMZ Z L L K K A C C C E E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196e3"},"rt":8463,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":558956,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196e4"},"rt":6010,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":565089,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196e5"},"rt":27993,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":593289,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"O Z Z F Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196e6"},"rt":46103,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":639517,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM02 PMM M X X I I I B 12 PMB B O F Z C X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196e7"},"rt":121401,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":761048,"subject":"BBPLJ","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35738","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"502 PMX X X M B B B B F F F F F C C C H H G I I I I B F F X X 02 PMC C J J J M M X X X X H K A A G G E G F F C C O X 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196fe"},"rt":27807,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":110060,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA A A C A A A A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f196ff"},"rt":9079,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":119242,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"2D D D E E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19700"},"rt":18367,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":137714,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C 10 AMC C C Z Z 12 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19701"},"rt":32982,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":170802,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C A U 5U U F Z O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19702"},"rt":79107,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":250019,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C I I H H 03 PM03 PM01 PMI I I O O 11 AMO O I O O 01 PM02 PMC U U U U F F Z A O O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19704"},"rt":11935,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":269573,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19705"},"rt":22911,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":292594,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19706"},"rt":21136,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313842,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19707"},"rt":31640,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":345586,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19708"},"rt":32490,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":378179,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F B B B F F B B 02 PMX X X F B B X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19709"},"rt":7774,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386058,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1970a"},"rt":8581,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":394746,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1970b"},"rt":22492,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":417346,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z Z Z O F F F X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1970c"},"rt":20549,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438002,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"E B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1970d"},"rt":64123,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":502234,"subject":"9XEMK","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32342","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMF F F 02 PMM M M E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19724"},"rt":32054,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100286,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AMO 11 AMO 08 AM11 AMC O 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19725"},"rt":57984,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":158371,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"D 11 AM10 AM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19726"},"rt":27666,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":186138,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I I C C A C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19727"},"rt":12257,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":198487,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19728"},"rt":101888,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":300469,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"A I K K F F U U U Z U F F F F U U Z F F O O I H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1972a"},"rt":7647,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":313480,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1972b"},"rt":15612,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329185,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1972c"},"rt":48520,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377803,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E G G B E J J J X X E E E M E E I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1972d"},"rt":27842,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":405739,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I I I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1972e"},"rt":123110,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":528941,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F B B F F F F O O F E I I J J J F Z F B B X 03 PMZ Z C G Z Z L A A L Z Z Z M M M B B M M M C C O O X M M M F F X 02 PM04 PM04 PM03 PMX M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1972f"},"rt":6154,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":535444,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"03 PM12 PM4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19730"},"rt":11017,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":546560,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19731"},"rt":15000,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":561654,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19732"},"rt":28074,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":589820,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM03 PMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19733"},"rt":57184,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":647088,"subject":"EH3ED","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29937","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M 01 PMX X X M M E B F I 12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMX M M M M M M M M M B B B F B F E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19744"},"rt":155626,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1052919,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM12 PM11 AM210 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM409 AM08 AM08 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM10 AM11 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMF D D 12 PM09 AM09 AMC C 11 AM01 PMZ Z Z Z Z 10 AM10 AM11 AMK Z Z 01 PMZ Z Z F F F F A 10 AMA A A I D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19745"},"rt":24444,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1077734,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D D D 11 AM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19746"},"rt":224905,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1302798,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,F","hovered":"C C 10 AMC C C U 01 PMZ A A C C C C C 10 AM10 AMC C 11 AM08 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM10 AMU U 01 PM01 PMF F 01 PM12 PMC C C C 11 AMI C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19747"},"rt":75713,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1379047,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"6504 PMD D D D D D 02 PM01 PM01 PMU U 11 AM10 AM09 AMO C O O O 09 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19748"},"rt":43885,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1423295,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM09 AM09 AM08 AM08 AMO A I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1974a"},"rt":10841,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1444892,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1974b"},"rt":88282,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1533361,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AM08 AMF Z Z 03 PM02 PMF 11 AM11 AMF F F B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1974c"},"rt":168652,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1702843,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B F 10 AMJ X X X 09 AMX B M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1974d"},"rt":43204,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1746644,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O J J J J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1974e"},"rt":5967,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1752851,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F B B 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1974f"},"rt":10397,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1763456,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19750"},"rt":9561,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1773196,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"10 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19751"},"rt":40271,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1813695,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19752"},"rt":33597,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1847492,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19753"},"rt":126589,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1974259,"subject":"HF78R","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34535","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19764"},"rt":51425,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":125329,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C C A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19765"},"rt":14227,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139671,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19766"},"rt":14788,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":154849,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C 12 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19767"},"rt":50671,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":206110,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"Z U A C C A A F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19768"},"rt":5200,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":211526,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1976a"},"rt":9663,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":226905,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1976b"},"rt":30401,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257425,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1976c"},"rt":64774,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322343,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I B B B 03 PMB M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1976d"},"rt":36414,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":359341,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J I J J I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1976e"},"rt":11201,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":370653,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"2F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1976f"},"rt":9392,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":380154,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19770"},"rt":9352,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":389619,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19771"},"rt":9725,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":399452,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AM12 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19772"},"rt":9490,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":409051,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19773"},"rt":7686,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416854,"subject":"91D56","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39427","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19784"},"rt":20582,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100846,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM11 AMC C C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19785"},"rt":10643,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":111586,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"F F A A A F K K Z Z K A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19786"},"rt":16236,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":127915,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19787"},"rt":8803,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":136824,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"F 04 PM05 PM06 PM06 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19788"},"rt":14911,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":151830,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AMZ H A A 11 AMI O O 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1978a"},"rt":20388,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":180622,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"02 PMJ G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1978b"},"rt":25355,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":206077,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C F J B B O O O 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1978c"},"rt":29074,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":235245,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"12 PMC E H O G G G B G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1978d"},"rt":28301,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":263708,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"H C Z N E F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1978e"},"rt":12555,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":276370,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E F 02 PM02 PMF F X 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f1978f"},"rt":15327,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291792,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M 12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMC 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19790"},"rt":5898,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297795,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"04 PM12 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19791"},"rt":19107,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":317019,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X X J H Z M J I Z N N 02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19792"},"rt":10538,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":327662,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM11 AM10 AM03 PM04 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f19793"},"rt":14077,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":341846,"subject":"RVTK3","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"26917","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"03 PM04 PM04 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMX 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f197a4"},"rt":31594,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58372,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O 12 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMH X X F 11 AMF U U U U F C F F C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f197a5"},"rt":10698,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":69174,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"F D D Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f197a6"},"rt":9592,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":78871,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"4K C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f197a7"},"rt":7184,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":86150,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"F F 04 PM05 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f197a8"},"rt":10362,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96608,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I I I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f197aa"},"rt":45557,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":147200,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6I I 08 AM09 AM10 AM008 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PMF X X G G G 10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PMO E 02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM06 PMN H 04 PMC 11 AMC C C C G C O C G B 10 AMF G 04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM04 PMG "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f197ab"},"rt":15821,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163122,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"08 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f197ac"},"rt":43838,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":207056,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G G G G E E F 03 PM04 PM04 PMO F O O O X O C G F 10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1511b8b1233c0f197ad"},"rt":23556,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":230714,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"F B B B I I I B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197ae"},"rt":10914,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":241733,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"7C 02 PM4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197af"},"rt":6698,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":248535,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PMH G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197b0"},"rt":4624,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253258,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197b1"},"rt":8295,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":261661,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"J X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197b2"},"rt":5442,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267208,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PMM X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197b3"},"rt":8747,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":276060,"subject":"QWPKO","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38841","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"M M 12 PM01 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197c4"},"rt":305939,"condition":"121","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1584521,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5411 AM11 AM11 AM08 AM09 AM02 PM11 AM11 AM12 PM02 PMA 11 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM5611 AM10 AM10 AM10 AMC 11 AM03 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM11 AM12 PM01 PME 11 AM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM05 PM04 PM12 PM11 AM01 PMC C C J X Z Z 01 PM01 PMZ U U U F 04 PM05 PM06 PM05 PM05 PMG B E E E B B 05 PM04 PM04 PMJ J J K K J J H B B G G K U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197c5"},"rt":142969,"condition":"121","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1727805,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"H D D 04 PMA F F 01 PM12 PM12 PMA O Z 01 PMZ Z U U U H Z 01 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM02 PMU F F H F H H Z 01 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM05 PM05 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197c6"},"rt":206463,"condition":"121","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1934583,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"C U C C 10 AM12 PMA O O A A Z Z F F F F H H H H Z Z 01 PM10 AMA O O I I 11 AM11 AMZ Z 01 PMU H H H H H J X K G G G D D 04 PMB B E E B 312 PM12 PM12 PMH Z Z 8B B G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197c7"},"rt":15379,"condition":"121","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1950270,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"A 04 PMD D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197c8"},"rt":252681,"condition":"121","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"2","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_impasse","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":2203060,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I I I 11 AMO 11 AMJ H H H J H H Z Z 01 PMF Z A K 03 PM04 PM05 PM05 PMD E B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197ca"},"rt":20495,"condition":"121","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2230973,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197cb"},"rt":22266,"condition":"121","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2253342,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I F B F B B B B B I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197cc"},"rt":38367,"condition":"121","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2291816,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"G L L H B B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197cd"},"rt":21516,"condition":"121","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2313441,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197ce"},"rt":99489,"condition":"121","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2413033,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B B F B B 12 PMI I B B M G 01 PMX X X O 03 PMH H O O 02 PMX X C C G C C 11 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197cf"},"rt":10353,"condition":"121","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2423792,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"3H B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197d0"},"rt":5442,"condition":"121","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2429338,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197d1"},"rt":45155,"condition":"121","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2474595,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z 04 PMZ Z Z H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197d2"},"rt":32041,"condition":"121","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2506745,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"X 02 PM01 PM02 PMM M M X X X O O O C C C 01 PM12 PMB B F 1E 10 AMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197d3"},"rt":65201,"condition":"121","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2572055,"subject":"1HLEP","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AMB B F E 02 PM02 PMM M M M B B B 12 PM12 PMB G 12 PM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197e4"},"rt":33390,"condition":"111","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":178857,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"H A A A A A A 12 PM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197e5"},"rt":13000,"condition":"111","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":191956,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197e6"},"rt":20356,"condition":"111","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":212408,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"5C C C 11 AM12 PM11 AM12 PMZ Z Z Z 11 AM11 AMZ Z Z Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197e7"},"rt":39317,"condition":"111","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":251821,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"F 02 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM11 AMK G 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197e8"},"rt":94241,"condition":"111","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":"1","grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":346160,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"U Z I I I I I O O A A H F 03 PM02 PM01 PMH H O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197ea"},"rt":5745,"condition":"111","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":359156,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197eb"},"rt":18071,"condition":"111","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377323,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"9J F X B F F 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197ec"},"rt":49623,"condition":"111","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427040,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5E E E E E E E F F F F E E F G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197ed"},"rt":28141,"condition":"111","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":455289,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"11J I 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197ee"},"rt":21331,"condition":"111","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":476723,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"12 PMZ M B B X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197ef"},"rt":9068,"condition":"111","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":485889,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"N X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197f0"},"rt":5286,"condition":"111","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491272,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197f1"},"rt":26290,"condition":"111","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":517656,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H 04 PM04 PM03 PM11 AM11 AM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197f2"},"rt":21622,"condition":"111","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":539373,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F 03 PM02 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6219b1521b8b1233c0f197f3"},"rt":26116,"condition":"111","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":1,"mark":1,"ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":565589,"subject":"4KH27","study":"SGC3A","session":"wi22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41210","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"M 02 PM02 PM02 PMK "}]
